Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1977 Coventry-- Meyer, G.. (Box 8)
  - Gaulin Corporation and Assn. of Engrs., Archts & DRFTSM L105 AAA #1130-0926-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Conference on Public Section Labor Relations 3/14/77, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - W.R. Grace & Company and Intl. Chemical Workers Un., Local 324 AAA #1130-1093-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. and Retail Clerks Intl. Assn.. Local. 1445 AAA #1130-0151-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Gulf & Western Eagle Signal Division and United Auto Workers; Local 1596 AAA #1130-0843-77 ARB 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hartford Electric Light Company and IBEW, Local 457 AAA #1230-0143-77 ARB 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Haverhill Gas Company and United Steelworkers, Local 12086 Direct ARB 1977, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Independent Nail Company and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1130-0577-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Jenkins Bros. and United Steelworkers; Local 5623 AAA #1230-0149-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - City of Lawrence, Mass. And Int. RBN. MBC&A PF 10 1977 Lawrence Patrolmen (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Leavitt Corp., K&R Warehouse and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1130-1319-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Learning Resources, Inc. and Distributive Workers, District 65 AAA #1130-0429-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln, Rhode Island School Committee and Lincoln Teachers Assn. AAA #1139-0971-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - City of Lynn, Mass. And Lynn BR. Mass. Police Assn. AAA #1139-1274-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Maremont Corp. and AC&TWU, Local 406 GR. #3354 FMCS #77K01047 ARB 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Maremont Corporation and AMAL. CLO & Tex Workers, Local 406 FMCS 77K06820 ARB 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Mass. Dept. of Public Welfare and SEIU. Local 509 AAA #1139-1391-76 ARB 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Massachusetts Electric and Direct ARB 1977 IBEW; Local 326, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Direct ARB 1977 and Service EES Intl. Union, Local 254 D (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Massachusetts Teachers' Assn. - NEA Arbitration Training No. Falmouth, Mass. 6/23/77, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - George J. Meyer MFG. Co. and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1130-0395-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1977 Morse-- Providence. (Box 9)
  - Mores Cutting Tools and UERMWA; Local 227 Direct ARB 1977 Gulf #921, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Morse Cutting Tools Co. and U.E. Local 277 AAA #1130-1421-76 ARB 1977, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - National Airlines, Inc. and NMB ARB 1977 WU S&S Division Case # MIA 33-75FR (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - National Blank Book Company and Graphic Arts Intl. UN. Local 48-B AAA #1130-0016-77 ARB, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education April 25-26-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - New Bedford Gas & Edison Light Co. and Direct ARB 1977 Bro. of Utility Workers of N.E. Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - New Britain, Conn. Board of Education and AAA #1239-0313077 ARB New Britain Federation of Teachers (Folder 1 of 2), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - New Britain, Conn. Board of Education and AAA #1239-0313077 ARB New Britain Federation of Teachers (Folder 2 of 2), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - State of New York Dept. of Mental Hyg. And Direct ARB OER # A-690 CSEA. Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New England Medical Center Hospital and Massachusetts Nurses Assn. AAA #1130-0736-77 ARB 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Telephone Workers U of NJ. Local 827 AAA #1330-0412-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Town of Newton Mass; Mass. And mass. Bd. PF-60 F10 ARB 1977 Newton Police, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - State of New York Dept. of Mental Hyg. And CSEA; Inc. Queens Devel. Center AAA#1367-0105-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hyg.) and OER File No. A-643 ARB DIR 77 CSEA, Inc. MH-Kings Park PC, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - State of New York and CSEA, Inc. AAA #1367-0125 (0117)-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - State of New York (Educ. Staff ODAS) and OER File #A-508 Direct ARB 1977 CSEA, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Norwell School Committee and Norwell Education Association AAA # 1139-1092-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Thomas O' Connor & Co., Inc. and Direct ARB 1977 Intl. RRO. Of Boilmakers, Local 29, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Overseas National Airlines ARB 1977 and NMB ALPA Case no. NY-12-768 ALPA (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Ozark Air Lines, Inc. and NMB ALPA #58-26-3-001-002-77 ALPA Flight Attendants, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Pan American World Airways and Sys. Bd. #C-76-94-HO ARB 1977 Intl. Bro. Teamsters NMB (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Pawtucket, RH. IS. City of Pawtucket Police Lodge #4 and AAA#1139-0044-77 ARB 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Town of Plymouth, Mass. And MBC&A Intl. Assn. of Firefighters, Local 1768 (Folder 1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Town of Plymouth, Mass. And MBC&A Intl. Assn. of Firefighters, Local 1768 (Folder 2 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Potato Service Company, Inc. and ARA Direct 1977 Bakery Workers, Local l 275 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Pratt & Whitney Machine Tool and AAA #1230-0219-77 ARB UAW; Unity Lodge 405 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Providence, RH. IS. School Committee and AAA #1139-0560-77 RB Providence Teachers Union, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Arbitration, Mediation, and Fact Finding: 1977 Public Service-- Yale. (Box 10)
  - Public Service Co. Of New Hampshire and AAA # 1130-0623-77 ARB IBEW: Local 1837, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sanford, Maine School Committee and AAA #1139-1636-76 ARB 1977 Sanford Teachers' Assn., 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - San Vel Concrete Corporation and AAA #1130-0230-77 ARB 1977 I.U.O.E., Local 877 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Trustees of Smith College and AAA # 1130-0432-77 ARB Service EES Intl. Union; Local 263, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - City of Somerville, Mass. And Mass. BD. No. PF 109-75 IARB Intl. Assn. of Firefighters, Loc. 1240, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - South Central Bell Tel Co. and Direct ARB 1977 Communication Workers of America, 1877-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Before Arbitration- In the Matter of: George M. Blades, Grievant 77-46-229 S, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Southern Aroostook Community School and Southern Aroostook Teachers Assn. AAA #1139-0984-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Southern Bell Tel & Tel Co. and Communications Workers of America ARB Direct 77 77-17-158, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and Communications Workers of America Grievance # 77-17-158, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - St. Regis Paper company and UPIU. Local 453 AAA #1130-1293-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Torrington Company and United Auto Workers, Local 1645 AAA #1230-0176-77 ARB 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - USM Corporation Fastener Div. and United Steelworkers of America AAA #1230-0278-77 ARB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - West Hartford Board of Education and West Hartford Education Association AAA #1239, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Town of Whitman Mass Intl. Bro. of Police Off., Local 509 AAA #1139-1197-77 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - City of Woonsocket, RH. IS. Intd. Assn. of Firefighters. Loc. 732 AAA #1139-0351-77 ARB, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wyndover Convalescent Home and AAA #1230-0070-77 ARB Local 1199, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Yale University and Fedn. Of Univ. EES.: Local 35 Direct ARB 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Arbitration Documents: 1978 American--Coldnnade. (Box 11)
  - American Biltrite Rubber Co. and URW, Local 309 AAA #1130-1416-78 ARB 78, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - American Biltrite Rubber Company United Rubber Workers, Local 209 AAA #1130-0643-78 ARB, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - American Bosch (AMBAC Industries) and IUE, Local 206 FMCS #78K07452 ARB 1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AMBAC Industries, Inc. IUE, Local 206 (LeClair, Senrty) FMCS #79K02216 ARB #GR 1863, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - American Bosch (AMBAC Industries) Direct ARB 1978 Gr. #1965 IUE, Local 206, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Amstar Corporation Sugar Refinery Workers, Local 1660 AAA #1130-1190-78 ARB, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Anderson Power Products United Auto Workers, Local 1596 AAA #1130-0760-78 ARB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Town of Arlington; Mass. Arlington Ranking Officers Assn. Direct ARB 1978 pay rates, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Armstrong Cork Company and United Rubber Workers, DALU #22619 FMCS #78K/08638, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bellingham, Mass. School Committee and AFSCME. Council 41, Local 1298 AAA #1139-1856-77 ARB 1978, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Beloit Corp., Jones Division and UER&MWA, Local 212 AAA #1130-0078-78 ARB, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bird & Son Inc. ad U.P. & A.W. - I.B.T. (Dauphinee) AAA #1130-1450-78 ARB, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bird & Son, Inc. and UP&AW-IBT Local #735 ARB AAA #1130-1802-78, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Boise Cascade Corp. and IBEW, Local 2144 AAA #1130-1628-77 ARB 1978, 1969-1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn. AAA #1139-1703-75 ARB, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - City of Boston and SEIU, Local 285 Gorham AAA #1139-0290-78 ARB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - City of Boston and Boston Police Patrolmen's Assn. AAA #1139-1188-78 ARB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Boston Daily Newspapers/ HeraldAmerican and Graphic Arts Intl. Union Local 300 Direct ARB 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Boston Edison Co. and UWUA, AFL-CIO Local 369 ARB 1978 1816 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Boston Edison Co. and UWUA Local 369 ARB 1978 P&M 1888 Singleton (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Boston Edison Co. and U.W.U.A. Local 369 Dumas senrty AAA #1130-1774 -78, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers Union AAA #1139-1194-77 ARB 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers Union Aides BC/BS AAA #1139-0068078 ARB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers Union AAA #1139-1055-78 ARB 1978, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - New Boston Garden Corp. and Boston Musicians Assn. Local 535 AFM AAA #1130-1685-77 ARB 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Bournewood Hospital, Inc. and District 1199 Mass. NUH&HCE RWDSU AAA #1130-1730-77 ARB 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Cambridge Electric Light Company and Utility Workers Union. Local. No. 392 Direct ARB 1978, 1974-1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Canada Dry Corporation and Distillery Workers Union; Kocal No. 8 AAA #1130-1307-78 ARB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Centerville Nursing Home and Mass. Hosp. Workers Un. Local880 AAA #1130-1316-78 ARB, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Charles River Park, Inc. and Firemen & Oilers, Local 3 FMCS #78k/20505 ARB 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Colonnade Hotel and Hotel, Rest. Etc. Union Local 26 Direct ARB 1976 Patino disch., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Arbitration Documents: 1978 Commonwealth-- Manchester Gas. (Box 12)
  - Commonwealth Gas Co. and USWA, AFL-CIO ARB 1978 Attendance (Folder 1 of 2), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Gas Co. and USWA, AFL-CIO ARB 1978 Attendance (Folder 2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - State of Connecticut and EUI Re: Marianne Kalbac ARB Direct 1978, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - State of Connecticut and CEUI Re: Richard Day ARB Direct 1978, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - DYMO Business Systems, Inc. and FMCS 78K19266 ARB 1978 IUE, Local 271, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Fall River Electric Company and I.B.E.W. Local Union No. 1465 AAA #1130-0847-78 ARB, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - General Electric Company and Intl. Fedn. Of Prof. & Tech. Engrs. 140 AAA #1130-0450-78 ARB, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - City of Gloucester and IAFF; Local 762 AAA #1130-1074-78 ARB, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - W.R. Grace Co. Organic Chemicals Div. and Intl. Chemical Workers, Local 952, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Contract Employers of the Graphic Arts Institute of N.E. and Direct Arb. 1978 (Pine) Boston Typographical Union No. 13, 1978- 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company and FMCS #78K/03942 1978 ARB IAMAW, Arrostock Lodge No. 1198 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hercules Inc. and United Steelworkers Local 12962 AAA #1530-0002-78 ARB, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Holliston, Mass. School Committee and Holliston Federation of Teachers Direct ARB 1978 Ray Neary (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Agreement Between Kaiser Broadcasting Company WLVI-TV, Boston and Local 1228, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC, Field Communications, Boston Globe, and Alphabetical Index, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Agreement- Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, Agreement between Boston Broadcasters, Inc. and IBEW, Local No. 1228, AFL-CIO and WSBK-TV/IBEW Technicians Contract, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Field Communications Co. WLVI-TV and FMCS #78K/12495 ARB wages IBEW, Local 1228, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Keyes Fibre Company and United Paperworkers Intl, Local 449 AAA #1130-0711-78 ARB, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Koehler MFG. Company and Direct ARB 1978 merit increases United Steelworkers, Local No. 3724, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Manchester Gas Co. and USWA Direct ARB 78, 1978-1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Hudson, New Hampshire School Board and Hudson Federation of Teachers AAA #1139-0520-78 ARB (Folder 1 of 2), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Hudson, New Hampshire School Board and Hudson Federation of Teachers AAA #1139-0520-78 ARB (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Arbitration Documents: 1978 Maremort-- Yale. (Box 13)
  - Maremont Corporation and ACTWU. Local 406 FMCS #78K08973 ARB 1978, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Maremont Corporation and AC&TWU, Local 406 FMCS #78K/17409 ARB 1978, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts 1978 and AFSCME Gagliardi CA-56 OER #77-124 Termination, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts 1978 AFSCME CA-55 OER #77-24 Demotion ARB Gallagher, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts 1978 and AFSCME CA-57 OER #398 Suspension ARB O'Neil, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts 1978 and AFSCME and CA-58 OER #17 Suspension ARB Paul Kelly (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts and AFSCME CA-59 OER #446 Suspension ARB Park and Perry, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts and SEIU, Local 509 and CA-100 OER #387 Termination ARB 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts MDE and Mass. Law Enforcement Council OER #77-913 Donald Watts Direct 1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mass. Bay Transportation Authority and Intl. Assn. of Machinists, Lodge 264 Direct ARB 1978 shifts coverage, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Electric Company B BRO. of Utility Workers Local 319 Dreec AR 1978, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Moore Company and DALU Local 22804 FMCS #77K22794 ARB Surreira, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Moore Company Inc. and DALU, Local 22840 FMCS 78K/16463 ARB 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Natick School Committee and Mass. Laborers Dist. Council Direct ARB. 1978, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - State of New York (Dept. of Criminal) and Direct OER #A-943 Justice CSEA, Inc. ARB 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Okonite Company and AAA #1130-1696-78 ARB IBEW, Local 1450, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Olin Corp. and FMCS 78K20195 IAMAW, Local 609 ARB 78, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - F.S. Payne Company and AAA #1130-1739-77 ARB 1978 IAM Lodge 264, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Potato Service Inc. and Bakery & Confectionery Workers, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Raytheon Company and IBEW. Local 1505 Direct ARB 1978 78-208 ACP (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Reece Corporation and AAA #1130-1365-77 ARB 1978 United Auto Workers, Local 1596, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - RKO General, Inc. and AAA #1130-1845-77 ARB 1978 IBEW. Local 1228, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Rust Craft Greeting Cards and FMCS #78K/11822 ARB 1978 Graphic Arts Intl. Union, Local 16-B, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Scott Paper Company and AAA #1130-0943-78 ARB UPIU: Local 9, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Semline, Inc. and Direct ARB 1978 Graphic Arts Intl. Union Local 16-B (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Sheraton Boston Hotel and AAA #1130-0107-78 ARB Hotel, Bartenders & Rest. EES, Local 26, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Department of H.E.W. S.S. Adl and FMCS 78K20604 ARB 1978 AFGE, Local 1164, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Warwick School Committee and AAA #1139-1352-77 ARB 1978 Warwick Teachers Union, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Warwick School Committee and AAA #1139-1264-78 ARB Warwick Teachers' Union, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Warwick School Committee and AAA #1139-1828-77 AR 1978 Warwick Teachers Union, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. and AAA #55-30-0242-78 Fed. West. Ind. Sal. Uns., 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Town of Whitman, Mass. And AAA #1339-0438-78 ARB IBPO, Local 509 Ed. Incentive Pay, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Woodstock, Vermont School Board and Direct ARB 1978 Woodstock Education Association (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Worcester Controls Corp. and AAA #1130-1881-77 United Steelworkers, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Worcester Controls Corp. and AAA #113-0661078 ARB United Steelworkers, Local, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Yale University and Federation of University Employees L.35, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Yale University and Direct ARB 1978 Federation of Univ. Employees, 1972-1980 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Arbitration Documents: 1979 Allyn-- Commonwealth Gas. (Box 14)
  - Allyn & Bacon, Inc. and AAA #1130-1922-78 ARB SEIU, Local 925, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - American Bosch Div. Ambac Ind. And ARB 79 Direct IFPTE, Local 112 A.B. Nunnally, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - American Bosch and IUE, Local 206 Grv. #A-1316 ARB 79, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Amer. Stratford Graphic Services and AAA #1130-0688-79 ARB 79 Brattleboro Typo. Un. Local 386, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong Cork CO. and FMCS #79K/13200 IBFO Local 47 Empl. Discharge, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Barrington School Committee and AAA #1139-1970-70 ARB Barrington Teachers Assoc., 1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Beiersdorf, Incorp. And FMCS #80K/00170 ARB USWA, Local 15536 Prod. Workers, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jones Div., Beloit Corp. and AAA #1130-1135-79 ARB U.E.R. & M.W.A., Local 212, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - BLH Electronics and IAM, District 38 Gr. Dept. 04 ARB 1979 Direct, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Borden, Inc. and FMCS #79K/11461 ARB ICWU Local 553 #M-12-28-78 & 78A, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - City of Boston and AAA #1139-0170-79 ARB 79 AFSCME, Council 93 J O'Brien, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - City of Boston and AAA #1139-1356-79 AFSCME. Local 944, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - City of Boston Gr. Paid Details and AAA #1139-0311-79 ARB 79 Boston Police Superior Officers, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - City of Boston Gr. It. Aldo and AAA #1139-0289-79 Boston Police Superior Officers, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - City of Boston (15-90) S-24-78 and AAA #1139-0024-79 Boston Superior Officers ARB 79, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - City of Boston and AAA #1139-0996-79 ARB Boston Superior Officers Fedn., 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - City of Boston and AAA #1139-0625-79 ARB 79 AFSCME, Local 1489 I. Pucci, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - City of Boston ARB 79 and AAA #1139-1517-79 AFSCME, Local 944 Class action, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Boston Edison CO. and UWUA, Local No. 369 DIR P&M ARB #1454 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Brockton Public Markets, Inc. and AAA #1130-0728-79 ARB 79 Brockton Retail Clerks Union, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Brockton Public Market, Inc. and AAA #1130-0874-79 RB 79 Brockton Retail Clerks' Union, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - C & S Wholesale Grocers and FMCS #79K/01254 ARB 79 Truck Drivers & Helpers Local 170, 1978- 1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Campbell Stationary and AAA #1130-0129-79 ARB 79 United Paperworkers, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Cape Cod Hospital ARB 79 and AAA #1130-0918-79 Mass. Hosp. Workers, Local 880, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Cape Cod Hospital and AA #1130-1493-79 ARB 80 Mass. Hospital Workers, Local 880, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Causeway Print and FMCS #79K/03785 ARB GAIU, Local 16-B Rates of Pay, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and AAA #12-30-0477-79 ARB UAW, Unity Lodge Local 405, 1974-1980 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - CIBA-Geigy Corp. # 78-152 and FMCS #79K/09604 Brotherhood of Chemical Workers, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - CIBA-Giegy Chemical Corp. and FMCS#79K/19700 ARB 79 Broth. Of Chem. Workers Gr.79-51, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Colonial Provision Co. and ARB 79 Direct UFCW Amal. Meat Cutters Local P-616, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Commonwealth Gas Co. and ARB Direct 1979 USWA, Local 12004 Gr. #9002-001 (Folder 1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Commonwealth Gas Co. and ARB Direct 1979 USWA, Local 12004 Gr. #9002-001 (Folder 2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - New Boston Garden Corp. and AAA #1130-0127-79 Local Union 1499 ARB 1979 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Boston University and AAA #1130-0964-79ARB 79 SEIU, Local 254 Costa, Granof, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Bow, N.H. School Board and AAA #1139-2119-78 ARB 79 Bow Education Assn. Personal Day, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Braintree Public Schools and Direct ARB 79 Vacations Braintree Cafeteria Workers Assoc., 1979 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Arbitration Documents: 1979 Connecticut, State of-- Kaiser Aluminum. (Box 15)
  - State of Connecticut and Direct ARB 79 CEUI/1199 Gr. Theresa Allen, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - State of Connecticut and Direct ARB 79 CEUI Gr. & Butler, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - State of Connecticut and DIR ARB CEUI Cooks- Mystic Oral School, 1973-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - State of Connecticut and ARB Direct 1979 CEUI John Daniels (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - State of Connecticut and DIR ARB CEUI G: Mary Loomis & Books, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - State of Connecticut and ARB 79 Direct CEUI J. Maddaloni et al, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - State of Connecticut and ARB 79 Direct CEIU D.philbrick, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - State of Connecticut and Direct ARB 79 EIU Gr. Silva, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - State of Connecticut and Direct ARB CSEA RE: Dental Plan, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - State of Connecticut and ARB 1979 Direct CSEA Robert Dagata (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - State of Connecticut CSEA ARB 1979 Direct Emily Kovacs, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - WM. Filene's Songs, Inc. and AAA #1130-1664-79 ARB UFCWU, Local 1445 (Folder 1 of 3), 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - WM. Filene's Songs, Inc. and AAA #1130-1664-79 ARB UFCWU, Local 1445 (Folder 2 of 3), 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - WM. Filene's Songs, Inc. and AAA #1130-1664-79 ARB UFCWU, Local 1445 (Folder 3 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Coventry School Committee and AAA #1139-0720-79 Coventry Teachers Alliance ARB 79, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Cranston School Committee and Cranston Teachers Assn. AAA #1139-1262-79 ARB 79, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - City of Everett and I.A.F.F. Local 1656 AAA #1139-1737-79 ARB 80, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Food Marts, Inc. and Food Handlers Local 371 E. Malone FMCS #79K/09471 ARB 79, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Town of Framingham and I.A.F.F., Local 1652 S. Arnold AAA #1139-0641-79 ARB 79, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)